要颠覆原来的生活是多么困难
It's so hard to turn your life over
迈出舒适圈
Step out of your comfort zone
要选择一个方向是多么困难
It's so hard to choose one direction
当你的未来尚未到来
When your future is unknown
这是不是一个笑话 有人会马上来把我喊醒吗
Is this some kind of a joke, will someone wake me up soon
告诉我这就是我们玩的一个游戏 叫做生活
And tell me this was just a game we played, called life.
我们是不是任由生活摆布
Are we, are we all really slaves
我们的所作所为
By the hands of ourselves
我是不是真的犯了那么多错
Did I really make all of those mistakes
我是不是真的慢慢衰老
Am I really getting older
为什么我如此迷茫
Then why do I feel so lost
这是不是一个笑话 有人会马上来把我喊醒吗
Is this some kind of a joke, will someone wake me up soon
告诉我生活是不是就是我们玩的一个游戏
And tell me this was just a game we played, called life.
当我们走到路的尽头 会有人在那儿等我们吗
And at the end of the road, is there someone waiting
我会不会因为一路坚持而获得勋章
Do I get a medal for surviving this long
这是不是一个笑话 有人会马上来把我喊醒吗
Is this some kind of a joke, will someone wake me up soon
告诉我生活是不是就是我们玩的一个游戏
And tell me this was just a game we played, called life.
这是不是一个笑话 有人会马上来把我喊醒吗
Is this some kind of a joke, will someone wake me up soon
告诉我生活是不是就是我们玩的一个游戏
And tell me this was just a game we played, called life.